// questions from https://www.englishclub.com/esl-quizzes/grammar/

export const questions = [
  // {
  //   "question": "Phrases are grammatical units that consist of",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "one or more words" },
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "more than one word" },
  //   ],
  //   category: "Phrases Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "A noun phrase with more than one word can consist of a noun and words that",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "replace the noun" },
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "qualify the noun" },
  //   ],
  //   category: "Phrases Quiz",
  //   needExample: true,
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "We like ________ our grandmother on Sundays.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to visit"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "visiting"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to visit/visiting"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "I might want ________ some money soon.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to borrow"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "borrowing"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to borrow/borrowing"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "My father hates ________ a tie to work.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to wear"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "wearing"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to wear/wearing"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "We can't afford ________ a vacation this summer.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to take"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "taking"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to take/taking"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "The company was pleased ________ your thank-you letter.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to receive"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "receiving"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to receive/receiving"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "Would you mind ________ a window?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to open"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "opening"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to open/opening"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "My suitcase is light enough ________ this time.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to carry"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "carrying"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to carry/carrying"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "She cannot leave the table without ________ her dinner.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to finish"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "finishing"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to finish/finishing"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "The music will continue ________ until you turn it off.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to play"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "playing"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to play/playing"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "My little brother dislikes ________ his hair brushed.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to have"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "having"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "to have/having"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Infinitive or -ing Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Can you swim?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "In a pool"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "Yes, I can"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "Very good"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Did he go to work or to school?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "To work"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "No, he doesn't"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "At 3:00 PM"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Has your class finished?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "Yes, it has"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "In five minutes"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "It's English"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Where is my pen?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "Because it's lost"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "On the table"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "No, you didn't"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Who did you visit?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "I visit my mother"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "Yes, I did"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "I visited Judy"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Shall we go to your place or mine?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "My place"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "It is yours"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "Yes, we shall"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "When will Lucy arrive?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "At 7 PM"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "No, she won't"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "From France"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Who called here so late?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "It's midnight"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "It was Ryan"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "Yes, I called"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Do you want to watch a movie?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "At the cinema"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "Yes, I watched it"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "No, I don't"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "Have you done the laundry?",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "Yes, I do"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "On Wednesdays"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "No, I haven't"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Questions Quiz",
  // },

  // {
  //   "question": "It is essential that she _____ at the meeting.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "be"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "is"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "If I _____ you I would call her tonight.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "was"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "were"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "It is necessary that every student _____ a uniform.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "wear"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "wears"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "I hope that he _____ his homework on time.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "finish"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "finishes"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "The doctors recommended that she _____ a holiday.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "take"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "takes"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "The boss asks that you _____ early for your first day of work.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "are"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "be"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "If he _____ feeling better we would go.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "were"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "was"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "It is important that we _____ home as soon as we arrive.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "call"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "called"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "The landlord requested that John _____ out of the apartment.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "move"},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "moves"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },
  // {
  //   "question": "We want the windows _____ washed before Friday.",
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": "be"},
  //     { "correct": true, "text": "to be"},
  //   ],
  //   category: "Subjunctive Quiz",
  // },

  {
    "question": `Which sentence is in the active voice?`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": true, "text": "John wrote the song."},
      { "correct": false, "text": "The song was written by John."},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `In the active voice, the action is done by`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": true, "text": "the subject before the verb"},
      { "correct": false, "text": "the object after the verb"},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `Adjectives are words that describe`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": false, "text": "verbs or adverbs"},
      { "correct": true, "text": "nouns or pronouns"},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `In which sentence is "fast" an adjective?`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": true, "text": "He’s a fast runner."},
      { "correct": false, "text": "He can run fast."},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `An adverb is a word that can modify`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": false, "text": "nouns"},
      { "correct": true, "text": "verbs"},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `In which sentence is "fast" an adverb?`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": false, "text": "He’s got a fast car."},
      { "correct": true, "text": "He drives fast."},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `Which of these articles is an indefinite article?`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": true, "text": "a"},
      { "correct": false, "text": "the"},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `Which sentence contains a definite article?`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": false, "text": "We saw a movie."},
      { "correct": true, "text": "The movie was great."},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `An auxiliary verb is used with`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": false, "text": "a proper noun"},
      { "correct": true, "text": "a main verb"},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },
  {
    "question": `In the question "Did you win?", which is the auxiliary verb?`,
    "choices": [
      { "correct": true, "text": "Did"},
      { "correct": false, "text": "win"},
    ],
    category: "Grammar Vocabulary Quiz 1",
    needExample: true,
  },

  // {
  //   "question": ``,
  //   "choices": [
  //     { "correct": false, "text": ``},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": ``},
  //     { "correct": false, "text": ``},
  //   ],
  //   category: ``,
  //   needExample: false,
  // },
]